https://demarr.com/terms-of-use/

Terms of Use
The services provided to you by Demarr.com. are subject to the following terms and conditions. If you visit or use this website or related payment sites (collectively “website”), you accept these terms and conditions. Please read them carefully. In order to use the services offered on this website, you must obtain access to the World Wide Web, either directly or through devices that access web-based content, and pay any service fees associated with such access. In addition, you must provide all equipment necessary to make such connection to the World Wide Web, including a computer and modem or other access device.
Demarr.com does not provide its services for minors, but it does provide certain services to adults who utilize a credit card, debit card, or bank account (via Automated Clearinghouse – ACH) from the United States of America. If you are under 18 years old, you may use this website only with involvement and permission of a parent or guardian. Demarr.com. reserves the right to refuse service, terminate or suspend accounts or service or cancel transactions at any time in its sole discretion.
Privacy
Please review our Privacy Policy, which also governs your use of this website, in order to understand our practices with regard to information about you.
Copyright
All content on this website, such as text, terms, graphics, logos, button icons and images, is the property of Demarr.com or its content suppliers and protected by United States and international copyright laws. The selection, arrangement, and presentation of all materials on this website (including information in the public domain), and the overall design of this website is the exclusive property of Demarr.com and protected by United States and international copyright laws. All software on this site is the property of Demarr.com or its software suppliers and protected by United States and international copyright laws.
Trademarks
Store Sense, and other Demarr.com graphics, logos, page headers, button icons, scripts and service names are trademarks or trade dress of Demarr.com. Demarr.com trademarks and trade dress may not be used in connection with any product or service that is not legally endorsed and authorized by Demarr.com in any manner that is likely to cause confusion among customers, or in any manner that disparages or discredits Demarr.com, its products or services or websites. All other trademarks not owned by Demarr.com. that appear on this website are the property of their respective owners, who may or may not be affiliated with, connected to, or sponsored by Demarr.com.
License and Site Access
Demarr.com grants you a non-exclusive limited license to access and make personal or business use of this website and not to download (other than page caching) or modify it, or any portion of it, except with the express written consent of Demarr.com. This license does not include any resale or commercial use of this site or its contents; any derivative use of this site or its contents; any downloading or copying of account information for the benefit of another merchant or entity; or any use of data mining, robots or similar data gathering and extraction tools. This site or any portion of this site may not be reproduced, duplicated, copied, sold, resold, visited, or otherwise exploited for any commercial purpose without the express written consent of Demarr.com. You may not frame or utilize framing techniques to enclose any trademark, logo or other proprietary information (including images, text, page layout or form) of this website without the express written consent of Demarr.com.. You may not use any meta tags or any other “hidden text” utilizing the name of Demarr.com or trademarks without our express written consent. You may not make available in any manner software viruses or any other computer code, files or programs designed to interrupt, destroy or limit the functionality of this website or any computer software, hardware or telecommunications equipment of Demarr.com or the visitors to this website. You may not interfere with or disrupt the services of Demarr.com. or the servers or networks connected to these services. You may not collect or store personal data about other users of this website. Any unauthorized use or attempts to use this website in an unauthorized manner terminates the permission or license granted by Demarr.com hereby.
Your Personal Information
If you use this website, you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your personal information and for restricting access to the computer or information, and you agree to accept responsibility for all activities that occur under your account. You should notify Demarr.com. and the entity to which payment was made immediately if you believe there has been unauthorized use of your account or any other breach of this website’s security.
Further, you agree to provide complete and accurate information as requested by this website in conjunction with the completion of your payment transaction. Any failure to provide complete or accurate information, or any attempt to use another person’s information, may result in cancellation of your payment and other legal action by Demarr.com or its assignees without limitation except as provided by law. Further, you agree to honor and make full payment of any transactions legally processed through this website.
All personal information provided to this website shall be kept in the strictest of confidence and in accordance with the Privacy Policy for this website.
Non-Disparagement Warranties
By entering into an agreement for services with Demarr.com and John A. Demarr, P.I., you agree that you will not disparage or comment negatively about the Company, its officers and management, and/or current or former employees. This provision shall include an agreement not to make any remarks in a blog, article, opinion article or any other publication not otherwise privileged, which tends to disparage, impugn the character, honesty, integrity, morality or business acumen, or abilities in connection with any aspect of the operation of the business of Demarr.com and John A. Demarr, P.I., or any of its employed or engaged investigators or support employees. This includes a warranty that any recipient of the professional services of Demarr.com and John A. Demarr, P.I. shall not, and shall cause its employees, agents and others working on its behalf, directly or indirectly, in any capacity or manner, make, express, transmit speak, write, verbalize or otherwise communicate in any way (or cause, further, assist, solicit, encourage, support or participate in any of the foregoing), any remark, comment, message, information, declaration, communication or other statement of any kind, whether verbal, in writing, electronically transferred or otherwise, that might reasonably be construed to be derogatory or critical of, or negative toward, Demarr.com and John A. Demarr, P.I., or any of its directors, officers, Affiliates, subsidiaries, employees, agents or representatives, or that reveals, discloses, incorporates, is based upon, discusses, includes or otherwise involves any confidential or proprietary information of Demarr.com and John A. Demarr, P.I., or its subsidiaries or Affiliates, or to malign, harm, disparage, defame or damage the reputation or good name of Demarr.com and John A. Demarr, P.I., its licensed investigators, owners, agents, contractors or employees.
Notwithstanding the foregoing, nothing in this section or elsewhere in these Terms and Conditions shall prohibit any Party from making any statement or disclosure required under the federal securities laws or other applicable laws; provided, that such Party must provide written notice to the other Parties at least two business days prior to making any such statement or disclosure required by under the federal securities laws or other applicable laws that would otherwise be prohibited the provisions of this Section 7, and reasonably consider any comments of such other Parties.
Any dispute arising under this provision of these Terms and Conditions shall be resolved in the same manner, and in the same arbitral forum, as is provided for disputes arising under other provisions of these Terms and Conditions.
Liquidated Damages
In addition to the foregoing, the Parties mutually agree that any claim made under the Non-Disparagement portion of these Terms and Conditions shall, when disparaging statements have been shown with reasonable certainty to have originated with you or anyone acting on your behalf, carry liquidated damages payable by you to Demarr.com and John A. Demarr, P.I., in the sum of Twenty-Five Thousand Dollars ($25,000) in United States currency.
Applicable Law
By visiting this website, you agree that the laws of the State of California, County of Orange, without regard to its principles of conflict of laws, will govern these Terms of Use and any dispute of any sort that might arise between you and Demarr.com for jurisdiction of any litigation or arbitration.
Demarr.com reserves the right to make changes to this website (including, without limitation, discontinuing this website or the services offered on this site) and these Terms of Use at any time, with or without notice. If any of these terms and conditions shall be deemed invalid, void or for any reason unenforceable, that term or condition shall be deemed severable and shall not affect the validity and enforceability of any remaining term or condition.
Demarr.com requests that you not use any of the information on this site, including without limitation the e-mail addresses that are posted here, to transmit, distribute or facilitate the distribution of unsolicited bulk e-mail or other such advertisements or solicitations to Demarr.com or any of its employees or agents, and any such use of the information on this site is a violation of the terms of use of this site.
Demarr.com has office locations in California with expanded resources nationwide and worldwide.
You can transmit your documents for process service directly to John A. DeMarr , P.I. by fax, email or U.S. mail.
Forms
Company Information
Success Stories
Contact Us
FREE CONSULTATION
Complete the form below to obtain a free quote for any of our services.
Please read the Disclaimer Privacy Policy.
Country
---United States (US)Aland IslandsAfghanistanAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelauBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBonaire, Saint Eustatius and SabaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBritish Virgin IslandsBruneiBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos (Keeling) IslandsColombiaComorosCongo (Brazzaville)Congo (Kinshasa)Cook IslandsCosta RicaCroatiaCubaCuraçaoCyprusCzech RepublicDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland IslandsFaroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard Island and McDonald IslandsHondurasHong KongHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIranIraqIsle of ManIsraelItalyIvory CoastJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKuwaitKyrgyzstanLaosLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacao S.A.R., ChinaMacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesiaMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorth KoreaNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalestinian TerritoryPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRepublic of IrelandReunionRomaniaRussiaRwandaSão Tomé and PríncipeSaint BarthélemySaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Martin (Dutch part)Saint Martin (French part)Saint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and the GrenadinesSamoaSan MarinoSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth Georgia/Sandwich IslandsSouth KoreaSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSudanSurinameSvalbard and Jan MayenSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandSyriaTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited Kingdom (UK)United States (US) Minor Outlying IslandsUnited States (US) Virgin IslandsUruguayUzbekistanVanuatuVaticanVenezuelaVietnamWallis and FutunaWestern SaharaYemenZambiaZimbabwe
Service Needed
---Accident ReconstructionArson/FireAsset Search: BasicAsset Search: ExtensiveAsset Search: Insurance SubrogationBackground ChecksBackground Checks: BusinessBackground Checks: Criminal HistoryBackground Checks: EmployeeBackground Checks: NannyBackground Checks: Pre-EmploymentBackground Checks: Pre-Marital/DatingCell Phone RecordsChild Custody SurveillanceCivil InvestigationsComputer Forensics/CybercrimeCorporate InvestigationsCrime Scene InvestigationsCriminal InvestigationsDeposition Officer ServicesDue DiligenceElectronic Data DiscoveryElectronic SurveillanceFinancial InvestigationsExecutive ProtectionForensic InvestigationsIdentity TheftFraud InvestigationsInfidelity InvestigationsInsurance Fraud InvestigationsInternational InvestigationsJudgment RecoveryMarital/Domestic SurveillanceMissing PersonsMobile Document PhotocopyMystery ShopperPeople Locate/Skip TracePolygraph/Lie DetectorProcess ServiceProcess Service: InternationalProperty InspectionsPublic Records RetrievalRepossessionsSocial Media InvestigationsStatements and InterviewsSubpoenasSubpoenas: Out-of-State and ForeignSurveillance/Activity ChecksTrademark ProtectionTrial PreparationTSCM / ECMVideo Surveillance/Photo SurveillanceWorkers’ Compensation FraudUndercover OperationsWrits and EWOsWrongful Death InvestigationsOther
What is Your Budget?
---$50 - $150$150 - $350$350 - $750$750 - $1500$1500+
By signing or submitting this form, you agree to the terms and conditions and privacy policy of this website.
